morning thought I'd do a bit of a a
review on a product that I've bought
it's um it's called Rocket Fuel by a
company called Savvy
touch um and it's a product that clears
your sinuses and it's targeted at people
for people with um sleep apne or um who
struggle with snoring on an evening or
on a nighttime people with a fever it'll
um help you breathe better
um so yeah I've been using it for a few
weeks now um I bought it I saw it all
advertised on social
media bit silly I know but I thought I'd
give it a go cuz um yeah with a bit of
air fever I don't suffer too badly with
it but just to help you breathing and
what this is is I open it up it's U
basically it's Manuka honey it's like an
orange it there you go it's Manuka
honey and you put a few drops on your
tongue
um yeah it's Manuka honey and it's got
menl crystals in eucalyptus oil
peppermint oil so basically
it's similar to Vick's Vapor Rub that
kind of
menthal um kind of vibe to it put three
or four drops on me
tongue and I can breathe I can breathe
better clear clearer so
yeah it does work the only problem I've
got is or the only issue I have it don't
last it um it only lasts for um maybe 10
minutes max so I can't keep just having
loads and loads and loads of this FR day
so um yeah my advice is it's a pretty
good product it's quite expensive about
40 quid a bottle in fact it's very
expensive my advice I'll probably give
give it 5 out of 10 because it does work
and it clears your sinuses I've had it
before bed it do keep me um Airways
clear all night um and probably after
half an hour I'm blocked back up again
so so yeah it's um but I suppose it's
good if I'm going to go out for a run I
can have it before um I can breathe a
bit better on my run and that's that's
about it so 10 to 15 minutes it'll last
um yeah that's that's my review 5 out of